Get ready for a chilling fun holiday adventure with the Ice Age herd!
Ice Age: A Mammoth Christmas is a animation, family, tv
movie film directed by Karen Disher.
When Sid accidentally destroys Manny's heirloom Christmas rock and ends up on Santa's naughty list, he leads a
hilarious quest to the North Pole to make things right and ends up making things much worse.
Now it's up to Manny and his prehistoric posse to band
together and save Christmas for the entire world!
Manny (voice), played by Ray Romano.
Sid (voice), played by John Leguizamo.
Ellie (voice), played by Queen Latifah.
Diego (voice), played by Denis Leary.
Crash (voice), played by Seann William Scott.
Eddie (voice), played by Josh Peck.
Ice Age: A Mammoth Christmas is a 2011 animated television special and part of the Ice
Age franchise, produced by Blue Sky Studios and directed by Karen Disher.
It premiered on November 24, 2011 on Fox in the United States and in the United Kingdom at
Christmas on Channel 4 and E4 and it was released 2 days later to DVD and Blu-ray.
This Christmas special takes place between Dawn of
the Dinosaurs and Continental Drift.
Despite being produced by Blue Sky Studios, the film's animation was actually done by some animators at Blue Sky and
mainly by the Los Angeles/Dallas-based special effects and animation company, Reel FX Creative Studios.
The film explores themes of holiday, prehistory, christmas, short film.